Finding Aid for the Katherine Philips Edson Papers LSC.0235
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Correspondence (1921-1933)
  - (July-August 1933), 65 pieces
    - Preston McKinney--Marion J. Harron., Industrial Welfare Commission, canning industry. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Mary anderson., National cannery code hearing, N.R.A., minimum wage conference. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Harriet Eliel., Fred G. Athearn, Senator Herbert C. Jones, referendum on Central Valley Water Project bill with amendments on power, League of Women Voters Living Costs project.; Introduction by League of Women Voters to Herbert C. Jones' article on water bill.; Senator Herbert C. Jones' article on Central Valley Water Project.; The portions of Senator Jones' statement omitted in League of Women Voters Bulletin. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Ann. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - (September 1933), 47 pieces
    - Marion J. Harron., Preston McKinney, canning industry, Reemployment Agreement, Industrial Welfare Commission. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - [Marion J. Harron]--Preston McKinney., Reemployment Agreement, canning industry, Industrial Welfare Commission. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Mrs. H.R. Champlin., Southern Conference of League of Women Voters. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - ?...--Harriet Eliel., Franklin Hichborn, Senator Herbert C. Jones' article on water. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Esto Broughton., New weekly on California government; Political Straws. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Harriet Eliel--Louise G. Baldwin., Names of Los Angeles League members to cooperate with Dr. Isador Lubin in Bureau of Labor Statistics project. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - L...W...B...--Mrs. Harmon-Zahn., Senator Herbert C. Jones' article, Fred Athearn. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Harriet Eliel--Louise G. Baldwin., League of Women Voters Living Costs project. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Edith Rockwood., League Women in Industry program. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Harriet Eliel., League Living Costs project, Dr. Isador Lubin, Paul Eliel and N.R.A. hearing, Fred Athearn, R.F.C., California water project and referendum. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Harriet Eliel., League Departments of Living Costs and Women in Industry, list of chairmen. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Frances Perkins--Mary Dewson. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Louise G. Baldwin., League organization, Muscle Shoals. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Belle Cooley., N.R.A. hearings, McCullough, Industrial Welfare Commission lack of funds, Chicago minimum wage conference. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Fern Clawson., League. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Florence R. Robinson., League, Women in Industry plus Living Costs, N.R.A. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - J...--Gen. Hugh S. Johnson., Recommending Katherine Philips Edson for Deputy Administrator of Canning. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Mary Dewson., General Hugh S. Johnson and appointment for Katherine Philips Edson. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Nell C. McKeen., League. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - A.B.C. Dohrmann., California sales tax, Ben (Schlesinger?), Edson family, Harrison Robinson, water project, power, tax burden, Industrial Welfare Commission, N.R.A., Democratic administration. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Idah S. Chadbourne, for A.B.C. Dohrmann. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - J.B. Lippincott., Observations in Japan and China, missionaries. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Harriet Eliel--Mrs. Ernest Wallace., Woman appointment to State Prison Board, Albert E. Boynton. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Harriet Eliel., League of Women Voters work. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Hester H. Schoeninger., League, Harriet Eliel.; Budget for Monterey Peninsula League of Women Voters, 1933-34. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Belle (Cooley)., Mary anderson, canning industry. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - (October-December 1933), 17 pieces
    - Lucile T. Moreland., Invitation to speak. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Grace B. Caukin., Civil service. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Mary J. Spalding. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Will J. French., George P. West, Mabel Kinney, Dr. and Mrs. Edward F. Glaser. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Mary anderson., Katherine Philips Edson's illness. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Mary anderson--Edythe Thompson., Katherine Philips Edson's illness. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Hiram Johnson., Progressive administration of past in California. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Ada Hememin (?)., In appreciation of Katherine Philips Edson. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - A.B.C. Dohrmann., Depression, N.R.A. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - E.R. Perry., Industrial Welfare Commission. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Will J. French. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - (Correspondence and Miscellaneous Lists), 52 pieces
    - (telegram) Mary anderson. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - R.I. Bentley. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Irma Buwaldo., Industrial Welfare Commission consolidation with Bureau of Labor. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Wallace Drew., Katherine Philips Edson's testimony before a commission. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Laura G. Smith. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Yoshi Shoda. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Frank Walsh., George Creel's article. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Chester Rowell. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Lillian Symes., Article. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Felix Frankfurter., Pilsbury's brief. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Florence Dennison., League of Women Voters work. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Jack., Frank Gooding, Warren Harding, national election. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Annie Wilson (?). (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Fremont Older., Praising Clarence Darrow, minimum wage, Arthur Letts, Frank Griffin. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - J...R...H... (Haynes?). (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - John Graham Brooks. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - William Hard., Criticism of article by Katherine Philips Edson. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Harriet Eliel., Mabel Kinney and Industrial Welfare Commission, minimum wage enforcement. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Helen H. Bridge--Mrs. Clarice Zion., YWCA resolution on minimum wage.; Miscellaneous. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Papers
  - Writings and Miscellaneous Notes of Katherine Edson., 72 pieces
    - Paper on World War I and the conservation of American freedom. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Speech on the Conference on the Limitation of Armament. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Speech on women's rights. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Material Concerning the Death of Katherine Philips Edson., 26 pieces
    - Sympathy letters and telegrams to relatives, including some from Will J. French, Hiram Johnson, and Dora Haynes. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Memorial tribute to Katherine Philips Edson at the Neighborhood Church, Pasadena,. Delivered by the Reverend Theodore Gerald Soares., November 7, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Notes and excerpts from newspapers on Katherine Philips Edson's activities. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Memorial to Katherine Philips Edson., 81 pieces
    - Radio address by Mrs. Berthold Lissner on the memorial to Katherine Philips Edson. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence concerning the memorial, from Will J. French, Fremont Older, Friend W. Richardson, Phil D. Swing, William D. Stephens, Hiram Johnson, A.B.C. Dohrmann, and others. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Circular from the Edson Memorial Committee asking for contributions to the fund. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Letter from Hiram Johnson on the occasion of the dedication of the memorial. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Photographs of the memorial site. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Biography of Katherine Philips Edson., 1 piece.
    - Copy of the Pacific Empire Press Reporter () with an article on Katherine Philips Edson., 1913 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings of and about Katherine Philips Edson
    - Newspaper Clippings of and about Katherine Philips Edson., 9 Envelopes. (Box 4)
  - Ruth Mccormick; Hiram Johnson; Progressive and Republican Parties; Minority Group Problems; Miscellaneous.
    - Correspondence of Ruth Mccormick (Mrs. Medill),, Concerning Republican Party Work., 1919-1920; 55 pieces (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Material Concerning Hiram Johnson., 66 pieces. (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Election material from Johnson's various campaigns. (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Johnson Speeches and Writings.
        - Keynote speech on non-partisanship in state affairs.., 1915 (Box 5, Folder 2)
        - Extracts from address in the Hughes presidential campaign. (Box 5, Folder 2)
        - Senate speech: Bring American Boys Home From Russia,., 1919 (Box 5, Folder 2)
        - Senate speech on the League of Nations. (Box 5, Folder 2)
        - Senate speech on immigration,., 1921 (Box 5, Folder 2)
        - Remarks in the Congressional Record,., 1921-23 (Box 5, Folder 2)
        - World Court, Back Door Entrance to the League of Nations, Would Involve America in European Intrigue. (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Envelope -- Newspaper clippings concerning Hiram Johnson. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Material regarding The Progressive Party and Women in Politics., 92 pieces. (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Women's Influence in State Legislation. -- Katherine Philips Edson, in the California Outlook,., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Election pamphlet on legislation interesting to women.., 1913 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - The Progressive Party. -- Chester Rowell, in the Fresno Morning Republican. (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Material regarding Chester Rowell's campaign for the Progressive nomination for U.S. Senator,., 1914 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - An abstract of six articles on the state's finances, by John Francis Neylan, from the California Outlook,., 1916 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Women in the Campaign. -- Frances Kellor,., 1917 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Speaker's Outline -- Record of Progressive achievements. (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Suggestions for Progressive Legislation and Policy in the Coming Congress,., 1919 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Lists of members of the Progressive State Central Committee. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Material regarding The Republican Party., 41 pieces. (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Article on Willis H. Booth, candidate for the Republican nomination for U.S. Senator,., 1916 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Republican Party Record on Woman Suffrage: voting record by party in Congress and state legislatures. (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Statements made by Katherine Philips Edson as a member of the Republican National Committee, concerning Warren G. Harding and James M. Cox, the League of Nations, and economy in government. (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Letter from Herbert Hoover to Woodrow Wilson on the League of Nations,., 1919 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Information on and report of the Republican Women's National Executive Committee. (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Recommendations for election platforms. (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Letter from Margaret Dreier Robins giving her reasons for supporting the Republican Party. (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Warren Harding's statement on platform planks offered by the National League of Women Voters. (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Statement of Margaret Dreier Robins, Presenting the Delegation of Women, on Social Justice and Women's Day, to Senator Harding...., October 1, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Hints for organization of local groups for Warren Harding in the election., 1920 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Lists of Names and Newspapers., 97 pieces. (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Officers of Progressive Republican Central Committee... and other leading Progressives. (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Republican State Central Committee members. (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Newspapers published in Los Angeles County. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Questionnaires., 109 pieces. (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Filled-out questionnaires on the Republican Party and on election issues in California, and a compilation of answers. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper Clippings Concerning the Hughes Train in the Election., 1916 (Box 5, Othertype Envelope)
    - Material regarding California's Japanese Problem., 46 pieces. (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Papers and publications on the Japanese problem by Katherine P. Edson, Chester Rowell, V.S. McClatchy, Col. John P. Irish, Dr. Yoshi S. Kuno, George Shima, Paul Scharrenberg, and the California State Board of Control. (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Newspaper clippings. (Box 5, Othertype Envelope)
    - Material concerning the Religious Persecution of the Pueblo Indians., 12 pieces. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous., 14 pieces. (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - History... and program of the California Economic Research Council. (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Conference of the California Economic Research and Statistical Agencies -- proceedings, and address by Dr. Alonzo E. Taylor. (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Operator's report on the political opinions of a Mr. Wieler of the Boilermakers' Union. (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Address on the Institute of Government, by Haviland Haines Lund.., 1921 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Social ideals of the Churches,., 1916 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - An Adventure in International Friendship. -- The World's Student Christian Federation. (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Saving the Redwoods. (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Report of Harris Weinstock to Governor Hiram Johnson concerning reports of the International Workers of the World and of irregularities in San Diego government. (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Names of members of the Senate Committee on Education and Labor, and of the House Committee on Labor. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Women's Organizations; Civic Groups; Government, Utilities & Taxes.
    - Correspondence and Articles on Woman Suffrage., 83 pieces. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Statements on woman suffrage from A.J. Wallace, Hiram Johnson, J.B. Sanford, Katherine Philips Edson, and Carrie C. Catt. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Statement on conditions in Kansas since women have had the vote, by Earl Akers, Kansas State Treasurer. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Two unsigned articles on woman suffrage. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Address in favor of a constitutional amendment... written for presentation to the Senate Committee on Woman Suffrage, by a Southern California committee of women. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Constitution of the National Alliance of Women Citizens. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Leaflets, Pamphlets, and Newspaper Clippings on Woman Suffrage., 35 pieces.; Includes articles and addresses by Carrie C. Catt, Mrs. Seward A. Simons, Katherine Philips Edson, Alice Park; anti-woman suffrage material; a section of the San Francisco Daily Journal of Commerce comparing Woodrow Wilson and Charles Evans Hughes on the suffrage issue. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Envelope: newspaper clippings. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - California League of Women Voters., 55 pieces. (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous issues of the Bulletin of the California League of Women Voters. (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - By-laws of the California League of Women Voters. (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Minutes of meetings and conventions, lists of committee members and projects. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - National League of Women Voters., 71 pieces. (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence and reports, and lists of officers. (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Material on community property legislation, the federal maternity and infancy acts, the proposed child labor and equal rights amendments. (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - List of publications of the National League of Women Voters,., 1932 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous issues of the Bulletin of the National League of Women Voters. (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Publications of the National League of Women Voters., 37 pieces. (Box 6, Folder 5)
        - Publications on the history, goals, and programs of the National League of Women Voters, including two addresses by the president, Belle Sherwin, plus lists of membership and publications. (Box 6, Folder 5)
        - A series explaining programs of the League of Women Voters. (Box 6, Folder 5)
        - Two kits, one on Muscle Shoals, one on Unemployment Compensation. (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Publications of the National League of Women Voters on Domestic Issues., 14 pieces. (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - Industrial Standards Recommended by the League of Women Voters Committee on Women in Industry. (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - Women and the Labor Movement. -- Mollie Ray Carroll. (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - The Convention and the Primary; Their Strength and Weakness. -- Charles E. Merriam. (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - The Federal Women's Bureau. -- Mollie Ray Carroll. (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - Electric Power and the Public Welfare. -- Ann Dennis Bursch. (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - Special Legislation for Women in Industry. -- Julia Margaret Hicks. (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - A Program for Unemployment. -- Mollie Ray Carroll. (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - The Wisconsin Plan of Unemployment Insurance. -- E.W. Morehouse. (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - An Introduction to a Study of the Regulation of Public Utilities. -- Julia Margaret Hicks. (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - The Problem of Disarmament. -- Beatrice Pitney. (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - The Pan-American Treaties of 1929. -- Beatrice Pitney. (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - Our Wants and How They are Satisfied. -- Mollie Ray Carroll. (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - Study Questions on the Tariff. -- Louise G. Baldwin. (Box 6, Folder 6)
        - Congress and Muscle Shoals. -- League Committee on Living Costs. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Proposed Equal Rights Amendment; National Woman's Party; Better America Federation., 38 pieces.; Material pro and con the Woman's Party's equal rights amendment, including contributions from Felix Frankfurter, Roscoe Pound, Ernst Freund, Dean Acheson, the National Women's Trade Union League, Florence Kelley of the National Consumer's League, the General Federation of Women's Clubs, Harry A. Slattery of the National Conservation Association, the National Woman's Party, Business and Professional Women's Clubs, and various lawyers. (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - List of members of Business Women's Legislative Council of California. (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Issues of and extracts from the Better America Federation Weekly News Letter. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - The Municipal League., 11 pieces. (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - National Municipal League:
        - The Aftermath of a Convention. (Box 6, Folder 8)
        - Epitome of Minutes of Meetings... (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Municipal League of Los Angeles:
        - List of Members. (Box 6, Folder 8)
        - The City Government of Los Angeles, California; Organization Charts. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Public Utilities and Taxes., 42 pieces. (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Statistics and Facts. -- Department of Public Service, City of Los Angeles; Bureau of Water Works and Supply and Bureau of Power and Light.., 1924 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - President's address, by Willis J. Spaulding, President Public Ownership League of America.., 1923 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Natural Gas; Our Newest Utility Problem... -- R.E. McDonnell, Public Ownership League of America.., 1930 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Efficiency of Management and Operation of the Los Angeles Municipal Bureau of Power and Light,., 1924 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Speech by Katherine Philips Edson on the power monopoly. (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Election pamphlet on the Hetch-Hetchy water and power project. (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Gas rates of 15 cities in California. (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - What Price Water? -- Los Angeles Bureau of Municipal Research. (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Consolidated Water for Los Angeles County. -- Los Angeles Bureau of Municipal Research. (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - The Boulder Dam, All-American Canal Project. (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Taxation of power companies and the proposed California sales tax: articles and papers by Senator Herbert C. Jones and by Franklin Hichborn. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Women In Industry; Industrial Welfare Commission; Labor Legislation.
    - Women in the Labor Force; Women's Land Army., 121 pieces. (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - General correspondence. (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Protective Legislation for Women. -- Council of National Defense, Circular No. 63,., 1919 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Pamphlets on the organization of the Council of National Defense. (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Pamphlets and information on the Women's Land Army of America. (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Women Workers in the Reconstruction Period. -- U.S. Department of Labor, Women in Industry Service,., 1918 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - National League for Woman's Service, program and Weekly Bulletin. (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Women in Industry. -- C.E. Knoeppel. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Women in the Labor Force., 34 pieces. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Standards Recommended for the Employment of Women. -- U.S. Department of Labor, Women in Industry Service. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Study in Labor Supply (Women) and Replacement. Alamenda County. -- Emily Olga Joseph. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - News Letters of the U.S. Department of Labor, Women's Bureau, on employed women. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Publications of the National Women's Trade Union League, including a leaflet in appreciation of Margaret Dreier Robins and issues of Life and Labor Bulletin. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Publications of the Industrial Welfare Commission., 38 pieces. (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Books and tables to be used in computing wages. (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Printed orders for: the laundry and manufacturing industries, mercantile establishments, general and professional offices, canning industries, hotels and restaurants, motion picture industry, nut cracking and sorting industry, and unclassified industries. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Industrial Welfare Commission; Labor Legislation., 28 pieces. (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Material on the Industrial Welfare Commission and on minimum wage, by Daisy Houck of the United Garment Workers, Katherine P. Edson, A.B.C. Dohrmann, and Ben F. Schlesinger. (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Amendments to labor statutes offered by Walter G. Mathewson, State Labor Commissioner,., 1927 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Justice Joseph McKenna's delivery of the opinion of the court in the Oregon minimum wage case. (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Brief and memo in the case of the People vs. Longmoor, concerning the California 8-hour law. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Industrial Welfare Commission; Labor Legislation., 53 pieces.; Material on the history and status of the California Industrial Welfare Commission and minimum wage, including statements by Katherine Philips Edson, the National Women's Trade Union League, and Marie L. Obenauer. (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Report on wages and working conditions in the motion picture industry. (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - A study of the wages paid in limited-price stores in California and in the United States as a whole. (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - An address on the San Joaquin Valley and its seasonal labor problem. (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - A speech on the canning industry by Katherine Philips Edson. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper Clippings. (Box 7, Othertype 4 Envelopes)
  - Minimum Wage and other Labor Legislation; The Depression; Related Domestic Issues.
    - Industrial Welfare Commission; Department of Industrial Relations., 33 pieces.; Miscellaneous material, including reports of the Chairman of Industrial Relations, 1933 [Timothy A. Reardon], and 1924. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Labor Miscellaneous., 24 pieces. (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Pamphlets on international labor organizations. (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - What the Emporium is doing [for its employees]. (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Labor Progress in Boston, 1880 to 1930. -- Ethel M. Johnson. (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Labor legislation for nurses. (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Radical Tendencies in the Industrial World. -- An address by Robert Hunter before the California State Conference of Social Agencies,., 1919 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - High-Brow Stuff vs. the Dinner Pail. -- Woodworth Clum. (Box 8, Folder 2)